const questionData = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which country won the 2010 World Cup?",
      answers: [
        "Spain",
        "Italy",
        "Brazil",
        "France"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Spain"
    },
    {
      question: "Which team plays at Old Trafford?",
      answers: [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "Chelsea FC",
        "Manchester United",
        "Manchester City"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Manchester United"
    },
    {
      question: "What jersey number does Kylian Mbappe wear?",
      answers: [
         "7",
         "14",
         "21",
         "28"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "7"
      
    },
    {
      question: "Which team does Cristiano Ronaldo play for?",
      answers: [
        "Manchester United",
        "Real Madrid",
        "Juventus",
        "Inter Milan"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Juventus"
    },
    {
      question: "How many points is a win worth?",
      answers: [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "Lebron James is a part-owner of which team?",
      answers: [
        "Los Angeles Galaxy",
        "Liverpool FC",
        "Newcastle United",
        "FC Bayern Munich"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Liverpool FC"
    },
      {
      question: "Who is the manager of Chelsea FC?",
      answers: [
        "LAFC",
        "Chelsea FC",
        "Arsenal FC",
        "Villareal"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Chelsea FC"
    },
    {
      question: "Which MLS team is based out of Seattle?",
      answers: [
        "Seattle Seahawks",
        "Seattle Sounders",
        "Seattle Storm",
        "Seattle Rain"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Seattle Sounders"
    },
    {
      question: "Lionel Messi plays for which team?",
      answers: [
        "FC Barcelona",
        "Boca Juniors",
        "Real Madrid",
        "Manchester City"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "FC Barcelona"
      
    },
    {
      question: "Which city was the 2019 Champions League Final played in?",
      answers: [
        "Rome",
        "Madrid",
        "Paris",
        "London"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Madrid"
    },
  ],
  currentQuestion: 0,
  score: 0,
};
